hala-hi.org 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy | Health And Life Africa Healthy-living Initiative (HALA)

Health And Life Africa Healthy-living Initiative (HALA) has created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy. This document explains how we gather, use, and protect your information.

At [www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/) and how it is used.

Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. We keep certain basic information when you visit our website and recognise the importance of keeping that information secure and letting you know what we will do with it.

This policy only applies to our site. If you leave our site via a link or otherwise, you will be subject to the policy of that website provider. We have no control over that policy or the terms of other linked websites and you should check their policy before continuing to access the site.

**Information we  may collect from you**

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site [www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/). This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * If you have provided your contact information such as names, email addresses and/or phone number to us, such data we may use such information to contact you for marketing and promotional purposes by various means, including regular mail, email or telephone.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, operating system, browser usage and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
[www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Confidentiality**

WE DON’T SELL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

While using this site, you may choose to submit personal information through email or online forms which will be recorded within our own database, not accessible to others. We will use this information to process your requests and we will not intentionally sell or distribute your personal information to third parties, except as required by law. If we share your data, it’s only with companies we’ve hired to do work for us to carry out the services you want. Examples of such service providers include vendors and suppliers that provide us with technology, services, and/or content for sending email, analyzing data, research, providing advertising and marketing assistance, processing payments (including credit card payments), and providing customer service. Access to your Personal Information by these service providers is limited to the information reasonably necessary to perform its limited function. They’ll never own it or be able to share it with anyone else. Your data is yours.

**Medical Data**

WE DO NOT COLLECT MEDICAL DATA OR PERSONALIZED MEDICAL INFORMATION.

**Collecting Site Metrics** ****

Currently we are using Google Analytics to analyze the audience of HALA Online and improve our content. No personal information is collected from Google Analytics. For further information on the privacy policy concerning Google Analytics, please go to <http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html>

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on [www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/).
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/) and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[www.hala-hi.org](http://www.hala-hi.org/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.hala-hi.org’s](http://www.hala-hi.org/) privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Governing law, consent to jurisdiction and limitation on claims**  
This Terms and Conditions of Use and your use of the Site, along with the Information contained therein, shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of  Nigeria without regard to conflict of laws principles, and you agree to submit to the jurisdiction of courts in Nigeria. You further agree that any claims or causes of action arising out of or related to this Terms and Conditions of Use and the Site, along with the Information contained therein, shall be filed within one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose, or such claim or cause of action shall be forever barred.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time and without prior notice, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we advise you otherwise. Your continued use of the Site or Services after this Policy has been amended shall be deemed to be your continued acceptance of the terms and conditions of the Policy, as amended. We encourage you to bookmark this Web page and review this Policy regularly.

**Related Policy** ****

**Last Updated: 02/12/2013** ****

**Effective Date: 03/04/2012**
